{
    "id": "1409b08356bf44e9a3086a0367cbdda7",
    "title": "Kinds of Sentences",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please leave your footwear outside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Where have you been all this while?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We will not tolerate this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am your friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister lives in Mexico.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do then?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interrogative",
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Do be a bit more careful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Never speak to me like that again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Always remember what I told you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Imperative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Interrogative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ball rolled slowly into the goal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Declarative",
                "Interrogative",
                "Exclamatory",
                "Imperative"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}